Your flag, your flag
is a splendour of sky
Crossed by the block, crossed by the block
by a block of snow;
And seen on its sacred background
Are five stars of pale blue;
On your emblem, which a roaring sea
Shields with its rough waves,
Of a volcano, of a volcano
behind the bare summit
There is a star, there is a star
of clear light.
To keep that divine emblem,
Let us march, oh fatherland, to death
Generous will be our fate,
If we die thinking of your love.
Defending your holy flag
And covered in your glorious folds,
There will be many, Honduras, of your dead
But all will fall with honour.
Your flag, your flag
is a splendour of sky
Crossed by the block, crossed by the block
by a block of snow;
And seen on its sacred background
Are five stars of pale blue;
On your emblem, which a roaring sea
Shields with its rough waves,
Of a volcano, of a volcano
behind the bare summit
There is a star, there is a star
of clear light!